yaskawa.com 2018-10-02

# Privacy Policy - Yaskawa

Last modified: September 23, 2016

**1\. Contact Information**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

Yaskawa America, Inc.  
2121 Norman Drive South  
Waukegan, IL 60085  
E-Mail Address: [marcom@yaskawa.com](mailto:marcom@yaskawa.com)  
Phone: 847-887-7000 

**2\. Introduction**

Yaskawa America, Inc. ("Company" or "We") respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the websites [https://www.yaskawa.com](http://www.yaskawa.com/) and [https://www.myyaskawa.com](http://www.myyaskawa.com/) (collectively, the "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On the Website.
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and the Website.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means; or
  * any third party, including through any application or content including advertising that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using the Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Paragraph 14). Your continued use of the Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**3\. Children Under the Age of 13**

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any Personal Information (as defined in Paragraph 4) or other information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information or other information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on the Website or on or through any of its features, use any of the interactive or public comment features of the Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please inform us by using the contact information in Paragraph 1.

**4\. Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, facsimile number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (" **Personal Information** ");
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as sex, date of birth, or occupation; and/or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners.

**5\. Information You Provide to Us.**

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website.
  * Your search queries on the Website.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, " **posted** ") on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (including but not limited to product reviews or customer comments or ratings) (collectively, " **User Contributions** "). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we may limit access to certain pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

**6\. Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies**

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and may include Personal Information. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies)**. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * **Flash Cookies**. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Paragraph 10.
  * **Web Beacons**. Pages of the Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

We do not collect Personal Information automatically, but we may tie this information to Personal Information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

**7\. California Do Not Track Disclosure**

The Company does not track its customers over time and across third party websites for targeted advertising purposes. Accordingly, the Company and the Website do not respond to Do Not Track signals. Third parties cannot collect any other personally identifiable information from the Website unless you provide it to them directly.

**8\. How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personal Information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * To improve how we provide information, products or services and in the development of new products and services.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide through it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
  * For market research and analysis for the purpose of product development.
  * For non-subjective statistical information.
  * For the implementation of related business operations.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, you may opt out by contacting us using the contact information in Paragraph 1. For more information, see Paragraph 10.

**9\. Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users without restriction.

We may disclose information, including Personal Information, that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our parent, subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and the Website.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which Personal Information held by the Company about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your Personal Information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**10\. Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the Personal Information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.  
 
  * **Promotional Offers from the Company.** If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt-out by contacting us using the contact information in Paragraph 1. This opt-out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions.

**11\. Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

You can review and change your Personal Information by contacting us using the contact information in Paragraph 1. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users.

Additionally, California Business and Professions Code Section § 22581(a) permits minors under 18 years of age that are California residents to request and obtain removal of content or information posted on the Website. To exercise such right of removal, you may contact us at the contact information in Paragraph 1 to request removal of content or information posted on the Website. Please note that any such removal requests do not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information posted on the Website.

**12\. Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at the contact information in Paragraph 1.

**13\. Data Security**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like commenting on blog posts. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of Personal Information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**14\. Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' Personal Information, we will notify you by e-mail to the e-mail address you have provided to us (if any) or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.
